Guide to the William R. Rambo Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Original Accession, 1939-1975
  - School of Engineering: Stanford Electronics Labs; consulting and research, 1949-1973
    - Electrical Engineering, Dept. of, 1949-1970
      - GE (East), 1957 (Box 17, Folder 52)
      - GE - Microwave Lab (Stanford), 1955-1958 (Box 17, Folder 53)
      - GE - Santa Barbara. Consulting agreements, 1960-1962 (Box 17, Folder 54)
      - Georgia Inst. of Technology, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 55)
      - Gibbs-Manufacturing and Research Corp., 1953-1956 (Box 17, Folder 56)
      - Government, U.S. (non-DOD), general, 1962-1966 (Box 17, Folder 57)
      - Gravity transportation, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 58)
      - Group leaders meeting, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 59)
      - Group leaders meeting, 1960-1962 (Box 17, Folder 60)
      - Gruen, 1955-1959 (Box 17, Folder 61)
      - Hallicrafters, 1955-1959 (Box 17, Folder 62)
      - Hughes, 1955-1959 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - IEEE (Inst. of Electrical and Electronics Engineers), Undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - IEEE Sixth Region (IRE 7th Region) Electronics Achievement Award, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Institute for Defense Analysis, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Intelligence Board, U.S. "Cost Effectiveness Task Group", 1965 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Inter-University Electronic Science Series, miscell., 1962 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - I.R.E. (Institute of Radio Engineers), 1955-1959 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - JHU (Johns Hopkins University) - Laboratory of Cooperative Research, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Joint Serivces - dead, 1954-1960 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Joint Services - Harvard U., 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Joint Serives - Technical Advisory Comm., - MIT Research Lab. of Electronics, 1960-1963 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Joint Services - various "JSEP" speech/papers, Undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Laboratory statistics, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Lee, Sang Bae, 1963-1972 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Lincoln Laboratories, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Litton Industries, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Lockheed - miscell., 1956-1965 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - McDonnell Aircraft, 1957 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Microwave relay data, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous corresp., dead, 1953-1964 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous non-technical, 1951-1955 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Motorola - Phoenix, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Motorola - Riverside Laboratory, 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Move: ERL to AEL, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Natl. Academy of Science: Naval Postgrad. School review, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - NCAR (Natl. Conf. on the Administration of Research), 1954-1963 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - NSA (Natl. Security Agency), 1958-1967 (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - NSA - Electromagnetic Propagation and Reception Comm., 1958-1962 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - NSASAB - security and conf/interest forms, 1962-1970 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Navy, 1951-1972
      - Applied, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - BUAER (Bureau of Aeronautics), 1954-1958 (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - General, 1951-1960 (Box 18, Folder 32)
      - General, 1962-1966 (Box 18, Folder 33)
      - Naval Research Adv. Comm.:expense account forms, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 34)
      - Naval Research Adv. Comm., 1968 Jan 10 (Box 18, Folder 35)
      - Naval Warfare Panel, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 36)
      - Navy Research & Dev. Clinics, 1962-1967 (Box 18, Folder 37)
      - NRL (Naval Research Lab), 1955-1959 (Box 18, Folder 38)
      - ONR (Office of Naval Research), 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 39)
      - Special Task Force for Surface Missile Systems (Reich) SRL, SEL, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 40)
      - North American Aviation - corresp., Binford, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 41)
      - ODRRE (Office of the Dir. of Def. Res. & Engineering, U.S. Dept. of Defense), 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 42)
      - Policy, laboratory, 1955-1958 (Box 18, Folder 43)
      - Position papers, 1969-1972 (Box 18, Folder 44)
      - Procedures, 1951-1958 (Box 18, Folder 45)
      - Program expansion, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 46)
      - Project Nos. to be assigned and information, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 47)
      - Projects - gen'l information on monthly progress, 1955-1958 (Box 18, Folder 48)
      - Publications, miscell. (including Ed. Comm. Minutes), 1955-1963 (Box 18, Folder 49)
      - RADC (Rome Air Dev. Center), 1954-1961 (Box 18, Folder 50)
      - Ramo-Wooldridge, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 51)
      - Rand Corporation, 1954-1960 (Box 18, Folder 52)
      - Raytheon, 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 53)
      - RCA (request only), 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 54)
      - Remler Co., 1953-1958 (Box 18, Folder 55)
      - Sandia P.O. #54-2612 contract, 1955-1958 (Box 18, Folder 56)
      - Security, 1954-1957 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - SEL (Stanford Electronics Laboratories), 1951-1971
      - Budget statistics, gen'l, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 58)
      - ERL double-decking, 1963 Feb (Box 18, Folder 59)
      - Miscellany, 1954-1958 (Box 18, Folder 60)
      - Office of Naval Research, proposal & contract Honr 225(24), 1958-1964 (Box 18, Folder 61)
      - Radar Astronomy, Stanford Center for, 1961-1963 (Box 18, Folder 62)
      - Radio Propogation Lab proposal, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 63)
      - Safety Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 18, Folder 64)
      - Senior staff, 1957-1963 (Box 18, Folder 65)
      - Staff Committee, 1958-1961 (Box 18, Folder 66)
      - State Department, 1960-1962 (Box 18, Folder 67)
      - Systems Components Section, Coordinating Committee, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 68)
      - Skilling, Hugh - retirement, 1971 Apr (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - SLAC (Stanford Lin. Accel. Center), 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Sperry Gyroscope, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - SRI (Stanford Research Institute) - NWRC (Naval Warfare Research Center), 1961-1964 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - STL (Systems Techniques Lab) - Coordinating Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - STL-ECM (Electronic Countermeasures) Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - STL - Reconnaissance Comm., 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - STL - miscell., 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - STL - Signal Corps, 1957 Jun 19-20 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Sylvania, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Task 24 - corresp., 1957-1960 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Task 24 - miscell., 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Task 24 - budget, 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Task 24 - proposals & budgets, 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Teaching, 1964-1970 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Trips - reports on, external ideas, 1951-1953 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Trips - reports on, 1956-1958 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Tube Program (2), 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - U.C. Berkeley, 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - United Airlines data - distributed on field trip, Undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - USAEPG Scientific Advisory Council (U.S. Army Electronic Proving Ground), 1959 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Visitors, 1956-1958 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Western Electric, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Speeches and articles (arr. chronologically), 1945-1974
    - RRL report OEMsr-411-209, "An R-F Wattmeter for the 1000 Mc3000 McRange", 1945 Jun (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - "Status of VHF Facilities for Aviation", Electronics, Vol. 20, #10, p. 90, 1947 Oct (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - RTCA, "Efficiency of Aircraft Traffic Control Systems", 1948 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - "Shoran for Surveying", Electronics, pp.112-117, 1948 Mar (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - AFC Circuit, Electronics, with J. Confalone, 1956 Apr (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - ARDC Electronics and Infared CM Symp. at RADC, "Current Stanf. ECM & CCM Research", 1956 Oct (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - ONR Military Operations Research Symp. (Host SRI). "An Appreciation of ECM Problems.", 1958 Mar (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - U.S. Naval Reserve BuShips - "Electronic Countermeasures ", 1958 Jul (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Stanf. Research Club. "The Research Program of the Stanf. Electronics Labs", Circa 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - ASEE. "Challanges and Problems in Grad E.E.", 1961 Jun (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Utah State and Univ. of - speech, 1963 May (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Research Coord. - new faculty - speech, 1963 Oct 22 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - JSEP Talk - Univ. or Southern Cal., 1964 Apr (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - NORAD EW conference - speech, 1964 Oct (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Academic Council - classified research, 1966 May 17 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - French Natl. Inst. of Aeronautics - speech, 1966 Sep 15 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - School of Ed. Advisory Council meeting - speech, 1967 Jan 20 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Speech given before student group - Old Union - informal noontime, 1967 summer (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Northrop - Stanford speech, 1967 Oct 17 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - EE 200 - speech, 1967 Nov (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Eglin - "What is EW", 1967 Nov 14 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Paper, "Import of Cutbacks in Federal Funding, of University Research.", 1968 Feb (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Stanford Days of Concern - speech, 1968 Apr 12 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Homeowners talk, 1968 May (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Speech for McCarthy, 1968 May 10 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Alumni Day - Land & Bldg. Development, 1968 May 18 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Stanford-NSF Symposium on "The Use of Case Material in Teaching Engineering" - speech, 1968 Jun 24 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - A.I.I.E. - speech, 1968 Oct 22 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - NCURA - "A New Dimension in the Administration of Gov't. Sponsered University Research.", 1968 Dec (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Campus Alumni conference speech, 1969 Sep 26 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Hawaii speech, 1969 Oct 14 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - UCSB talk, 1969 Dec 2 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Engr. 296B - Dr. Skilling, talk, 1970 Apr 16 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Dean's Institute, Miami, Fla. - speech, 1970 May 4 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - UCLA conference, 1970 May 20 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Pres. Pitzer dinner - speech, 1970 Jul 23 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - "Engineering Research in Transition" - paper, 1970 Oct (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Alf Brandin's going away - speech, 1971 Apr (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Stanford Associates speech, 1971 Jun 17 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Pettit Dinner, 1972 Feb 5 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - NCAR, New Orleans - speech (later pub. in Research Management), 1972 Oct (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Honolulu - speech, 1974 Mar (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Personal and miscellaneous material, 1939-1974
    - Biographical material, 1951-1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Career data - miscell., 1939-1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, 1958-1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Clearance papers - security & financial interests, 1951-1968 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - miscellaneous, 1970-1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Gov't. consulting, 1959-1969 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Gov't. consulting/expense reports, 1966-1969 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - NDRC Division 15, 1963-1966 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Old Crows, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Prof. societies/memberships, etc., 1954-1972 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Publications - lists of, 1957-1966 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Security & financial interests, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Additional Material, 1961-1991; Accession ARCH-1997-093
  Inventory provided by Dr. Rambo for Accession ARCH-1997-093
  Box/folder in ()
  1966 - 1 (6/7) The story begins in 1966 because classified research (and DoD research in general) surfaced as a major issue. The special attention was initiated by an expose at Michigan State involving the CIA. It peaked at Stanford in a special meeting of the entire Academic Council at which I was to appear for questioning (17 May). The file contains a prescient hand-written note dated May 10 from C.J. Shoens, the Director of STL.
  1967 - 1 (6/8) The very thin file reflects a quiet year in the areas of direct concern here. There are a few exchanges with the Baxter Committee which had been set up to monitor classified research.
  1968 - 1 (6/9) This was a dark year. Unrest built, and following a week that included two sit-ins and an $80,000 arson loss, the Faculty conceded the contest via an Academic Council vote on 8 May. The new policy of appeasement was not lost on student dissidents. They returned in September with a revealing set of "non-negotiable demands" (File 1968 - 2M). Kenneth Pitzer, Stanford's Neville Chamberlain, arrived in early December. This file became quite full following Registration on 23 September.
  1968 - 3P (6/12) The local focus is here interrupted by two files containing press reports (hence an added P). This first relates to the major happenings in the 1968-69 academic year to the mid-April AEL sit-in. These newspaper accounts add an outside perspective.
  1969 - 1P (7/1) The 9-day AEL sit-in is covered by the Stanford News Service.
  1969 - 3 (7/14) This file reports the 1968-69 academic year to the end of the AEL sit-in as viewed from AEL. It reveals that even before the end of the sit-in, a number of individuals had decided to leave the University because of now obvious incapacities of the Community.
  1969 - 4 (7/5-6)The AEL story continues from late April through May. Having received its freedom from the University, SRI agreed to take over the disputed contracts and the now-disenchanted staff members.
  1969 - 5 (7/7) June and July. The government research sponsors agreed to the transfer of the disputed work to SRI. The approval came via an intense effort spearheaded by C.J. Shoens, with strong support from SRI and the Stanford Contracts Office.
  1969 - 6 (7-8) August through December. By the end of the year the STL program was gone -- a clear victory for the dissidents. But it was in part a pyrrhic victory. STL researchers were at home in SRI, the old program in place. Only the traditional university overview was gone. A second group had formed a start-up company focussed on military electronics. SRI was now completely independent. And the Administration had embarked quietly on an aggressive relationship with the DoD -- so aggressive as to be decried by F. E.Terman in a 22 October 1970 note in my Reading File.
  1969 - 7 (7/9)In the AEL sit-in affair, some actions and attitudes of the Administration, and of some others in responsible roles, are here recorded.
  (As a 1997 aside) I am in touch with several members of the former STL staff. Even after almost 30 years, a disaffection with Stanford remains in varying degrees. But the forced departure of these particularly talented individuals is now viewed by most as truly fortunate. (One may doubt that a Stanford career would have produced an 11000 sq ft winter home that is just being finished in Indian Wells.)
  1969 - 9 (8/2) This file deals with the University/SRI relationship. The excesses leading up to, and during the AEL sit-in, were not lost on the Trustees, nor on the SRI management and staff. Two weeks after the sit-in, SRI gained its freedom via Trustee action. Four days of riots followed the decision.
  1969 - 10 (8/3) The McClellan Hearings. In large part because of the publicity attending recent Stanford events, Messrs. Pitzer, Lyman, Friedenthal (Law) and Rambo were ordered to appear on 1 & 2 July before the U.S. Senate Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations. The Chairman, Senator McClellan, had scheduled appearances for six of the more troubled universities and Stanford ranked first.
  The very real threat was the imposition of Government oversight on University operations via control of research funds. A counter argument was that Stanford now was prepared to handle these troubles alone. As events over the next two years proved, that argument was certainly not true. But it went over so well that we were dismissed and the appearances of the other schools were cancelled.
  1970 - (8/5) Another eventful Spring. I had occasion to comment on it at a Dean's meeting in Florida on 4 May ........ "In the month just ended, we have had a $100,000 fire, three more sit-ins, police on campus on six different occasions, over 30 injuries to demonstrators and police alike, and more than $100,000 in damage due to vandalism apart from arson. We had a militant class boycott last Friday, and a full-fledged strike is scheduled for today. Three key demands are -- The U.S. to get out of Southeast Asia, freedom for all political prisoners, and no University association with the DoD."
  For sentimental reasons, the last demand moved me to include in this folder the 1970 proposal for the annual renewal of a longstanding DoD contract. It had been funded by the Army, Navy, and Air Force for almost 20 years and I had been the Principal Investigator for most of that time; this was my last proposal because of early retirement plans. None of the research was ever classified, some support for 20-25 faculty was typical, as was the participation of 25-30 graduate students. The DoD contract had thusly funded the research for perhaps 10-12 PhDs each year for a very long time.
  1970 - 2 (8/6) While the Spring was difficult for everyone, a local focus was on the travails of the Durand Building. It was "trashed" quite frequently (as demonstrated by the coverage in the Photo Album). The Aero and Astro people and the RSL staff handled it remarkably well -- with a touch of humor. On one dark night when the rocks were flying, a defender on a balcony above shouted out, "IS THE (non existent )LASER READY?" The street below was empty in about ten seconds!
  1970 - 3 (8/7) President Pitzer resigned on 25 June. My membership on the Faculty Presidential Search Committee accounts for this file.
  1971 - 1P (8/8) Another truly dismal Spring is addressed in this file. Because of the far-ranging events, the best coverage is in the news releases from the Stanford News Service.
  1971 - 2 (8/9) The CIA revisited. This minor irritation returns us to 1966 and was quite peripheral to the springtime events. The file is self-explanatory.
  1971 - 3 (8/10) A not so minor irritation was the so-called SWOPSI exercise. It was imposed on a tired and disinterested faculty and the product was to be two more reports on DoD research at Stanford. Since these were to be developed by students the effort was deemed justified. The file concludes with three responses to these Final Reports. One is from Dean Pettit's office and deals with volume I (with data, but deferred conclusions). Volume II (with conclusions) generated two objections. Professor Kline (Mechanical Engineering) was quite acerbic. The paper from Dr. Kincheloe (STL) is well worth reading.
  The time period covered in these files ended in 1971. (By Winter, Mrs. Rambo and I were into a trip to South Korea where I was a consultant on the development of a new Graduate Engineering School. There were anti-aircraft guns on the hotel roof in Seoul and manned machine-gun emplacements along the highways; it seemed peaceful to us after Stanford.
  Three folders remain which I find particularly interesting. They contain papers, booklets, rank propaganda, etc., prepared and distributed by the opposition, students and outsiders, during the 1968-1969 Academic Year. The material was collected by the AEL staff and students and was kept in my office files.
  There are some thoughtful discussions of purposes and plans - - and ranting against the Pigs. A few essays are more perceptive than some faculty products of the same era. There are instructions on how to make pipe bombs. Much of the material is undated (and unsigned) but I have tried to arrange a chronology of sorts.
  1968 - 2M (6/10-11) The M is for Militant (recognizing the spectrum of actions undertaken). The file continues to mid-1969. By then, the local interest in collecting the material had disappeared.
  1969 - 2M (7/2-3) Many of these items were produced in the publications area in the AEL basement during the sit-in. The file has a bonus. During the sit-in, the song "Rambo Rambo" was produced and received some notoriety. I chanced on a copy a few years ago in a small store up the Peninsula. It is the first (1 min) song on the audio tape in this folder (The words are attached.) It is not a Golden Oldie.
  1969 - 8M (8/1) This was a short April period marked by the unsuccessful effort to persuade, or coerce, the University and SRI to merge.
  The M files expose the remarkable diversity in both the issues and participants in these events. They refute the popular present misconception that the period belonged to "deeply concerned Stanford students" protesting the Vietnam War and Draft. Actually, in one of the court injunctions obtained in the period, ten of the twelve identified organizations were off-campus groups. (The SDS was listed as one of the two groups legally on campus.)
  Why is this important? Because it is unfair to leave only "concerned Stanford students" with the sordid history of a halfdozen major cases of arson (including President Sterling's office just before he was to retire). There were many others involved in the thoughtless trashing and vandalism, in the firing of shotguns and rifles at buildings and homes (and eventually people), in the breaking and entering and theft, and on and on. It is important that the outsiders not slip away again -- this time, out of the history.
  There are two boxes with reading files, sequenced from 1961 through 1971.
  The final item is a photo album. The pictures are associated with three of the early events -- The AEL and Encina sit-ins in 1969 and the vandalism impact on the Durand Building a year later. There is a Table of Contents.
  The series is arranged in three subseries: 1. Chron file, 1961-1991. 2. Student unrest, 1966-1971. 3. Photo album - AEL during sit-in of April 1969; Encina April 1969; vandalism at Durand Building early 1970. Most photos taken by Lloyd Provan, the University photographer, undated.
  - Chron file, 1961-1991
    - 1961 Oct-Dec (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1962 Jan-Mar (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1962 Apr-May (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1962 Jun-Jul (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1962 Aug-Oct (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1962 Nov-Dec (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1963 Jan-Feb (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1963 Mar-Apr (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1963 May-Jul (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1963 Aug-Sep (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1963 Oct (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1963 Nov-Dec (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1964 Jan-Mar (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1964 Apr (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 1964 May (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 1964 Jun-Jul (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 1964 Aug-Sep (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 1964 Oct-Dec (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 1965 Jan (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 1965 Feb (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 1965 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 1965 May-Jun (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 1965 Jul-Aug (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1965 Sep-Oct (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1965 Nov-Dec (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1966 Jan-Feb (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1966 Mar (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 1966 Apr-Jun (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 1966 Jul-Aug (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 1966 Sep-Dec (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 1967 Jan-Mar (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 1967 Apr-May (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 1967 Jun-Jul (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 1967 Aug-Sep (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 1967 Oct-Dec (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 1968 Jan-Feb (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 1968 Mar-Apr (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 1968 May-Jun (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 1968 Jul-Sep (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 1968 Oct–Dec (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 1969 Jan-Feb (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 1969 Mar-Apr (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 1969 May-Jul (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 1969 Aug-Nov (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 1969 Dec (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - 1970 Jan (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - 1970 Feb (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 1970 Mar (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 1970 Apr-May (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 1970 Jun (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 1970 Jul-Aug (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 1970 Sep-Oct (Box 5, Folder 2)